<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Women Security</string>
    <string name="app_info">Women Security\n(Please Insert Your Information)</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!--User Name-->
    <string name="me">Name:Md.Jumaer Ahamed (Bsc in CSE)</string>



    <string name="dev">Design &amp; Developed By</string>

    <!--Settings-->
    <string name="police_txt"> Police Number: </string>
    <string name="police_number">01737512549</string>
    <string name="primary_txt">Number 1: </string>
    <string name="secondary_txt">Number 2: </string>
    <string name="num">017</string>
    <string name="title_activity_gps_track">Map</string>

    <string name="kick">

When someone attacks you in a place where you have no chance to run or to ask for help.
You have no choice but to fight.Of course the attacker will be more expert in this case so you will have to use your brain when you fight.
Hit on his pressure points so that even if you get a chance to hit him once u can make that one hit count.</string>


    <string name="knife">Nowadays no place is safe. So everyone should have something with them that can be useful in emergency.
Disguised weapons like the knives showed in the picture can be very useful in emergencies.</string>

    <string name="punch">If the attacker greps you from the front and you can not move your legs you will have to use ur hands to get free.
Use your hands to punch him. Just punch with all ur might.</string>

    <string name="scream">

If ur in a situation where you cant fight can not run the only choice left for you is to shout just shout as loud as u can.
it will help u to seek the attention of other people and it will definitely startle the attacker.</string>

    <string name="spray">One of the best weapons you can use in emergency is a pepper spray.
It is easy to find and you can take it anywhere.But you have to be careful when you use it.
Keep in mind that it will work the best if you spray it into the attackers eyes or nose.
Otherwise it wont affect him.But if you can get his eyes or nose a pepper spray can surely be a life saver for anyone.</string>
</resources>
